

Raluca Gui

University of Zurich • Department of Business Administration • Chair of Marketing and Market Research • Andreasstrasse 15 • 8050 Zurich • raluca.gui@business.uzh.ch • +49 (176) 998-43452

Summary

I have a BA in Mathematics and an MA in Statistics and Marketing. I am currently pursuing my PhD in Marketing and Social Networks at University of Zurich. I am expected to graduate from the PhD by the end of this year. I have extensive knowledge of statistical methods using different statistical software such as R, Stata and

Python, as well as Machine Learning competencies. I have been teaching Statistics, Quantitative Methods and Machine Leaning for more than 5 years. I have been working in an cross-cultural environment for more than 10 years. I speak fluently English, French, Spanish, Bulgarian and Romanian, and I have two children.

Experience

University of Zurich

ZURICH, SWITZERLAND

Research Associate

May 2013 - September 2018

I teach Master level courses in Marketing Analytics and Machine Learning.

Universidad Carlos III de Madrid

Madrid, Spain

Teaching Associate

Sep 2009 - Sep 2012

I taught undergraduate level courses in Statistics I and II, Marketing and Operations Management, both in English and Spanish.

IBM Global Financing

BUDAPEST, HUNGARY

Business Support Operations Specialist

Aug 2006 - Aug 2007

I was in charge of managing the lease portfolio, settlement, end of lease decisions, as well as reporting and audit support activities. Due to my involvement and perseverance in training the new employees, I have received the "Employee of the Month" award.

Central European University (CEU) - Labor Project

Budapest, Hungary

Research Assistant

June 2005 - Sep 2005

The CEU Labor Project conducts academic and policy-relevant research on labor markets and other applied microeconomic issues in Central and Eastern Europe. My responsibilities as RA were in statistical analysis (using Stata) of large employer-employee matched datasets, as well as in data mining and data cleaning.

Laboratoire Logiciels Systemes et Reseaux (LSR-IMAG)

Grenoble, France

Research Assistant

June 2003 - Sep 2003

The LSR -IMAG Laboratory research contributes to the progress in technologies for the development of large scale software systems. Such systems are characterised by very large software sizes, large teams working on them, large amount of data manipulated, and a highly distributed nature. As part of the team, I was assigned to develop in JAVA an analyser and evaluator of algebraic expressions for evaluating equations and constraints for the 2nd version of AROM - an object oriented database system.

Education

University of Zurich Zurich, Switzerland **PhD in Marketing**May 2013 - September 2018 (expected)

Universidad Carlos III de Madrid

MADRID, SPAIN

MA in Quantitative Methods

Sep 2007 - June 2009

Major: Marketing and Statistics

Central European University

MA in Economics

Budapest, Hungary

Sep 2004 - June 2006

Babes - Bolyai University Cluj-Napoca, Romania
BA in Mathematics Sep 2000 - June 2004

Skills

Technical specialties: R, Matlab, Stata, SPSS; Tableau; LaTeX, Keynote, PowerPoint.

Languages: Romanian (mother tongue), English (fluent), French (fluent), Spanish (intermediate), German (basic), Bulgarian (basic).